igofx.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy – IGOFX

#### Objectives

IGOFX is taking its clients’ privacy as the utmost priority in this business. The company recognizes and respects the basic human right of privacy with full ethic of running the business. Since the client is the key of our business, we take pride and full responsibility in providing security on the client’s personal information and privacy. The provisions of this notice apply to all our clients and also service provider.

#### Personal Information

##### Basic information

Information that you provide to us upon application for trading account and other forms, such as your name, address, birth date, Social Security number, occupation, assets, and income.

##### Transaction information

Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates as well as information about our communications with you which include your account balances, trading activity, your inquiries, and our responses.

##### Verification information

Information required verifying your identity and residential status, such as a passport or driver’s license. Examples also include background information about you we receive from public records or from other entities not affiliated with IGOFX.

#### Information Sharing

##### Affiliates

IGOFX may share your personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as, but not limited to, servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, or to aid in the trading activity of the company, its affiliates, or employees, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as companies that have an ownership interest in our company and authorized representatives from us. The information we share with affiliates may include basic information such as your name, address, transaction record and account information. Our affiliates are responsible to maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent of IGOFX does in accordance with this Policy.

##### Third Parties

Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with IGOFX, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to us. Non-affiliated companies that assist IGOFX in providing services to you are required to fulfill the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that we dictates.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your request or pursuant to your expressed consent.

##### Regulatory Disclosure

IGOFX may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property.

#### Internet Security

##### About Cookies

Cookies are files containing information that a website uses to track its visitors. IGOFX may set and access our cookies in your system, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring you to us. IGOFX or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with our products and services to track your activities on our website. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable.

##### Security Technology

IGOFX is equipped with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submitting to us. This is to protect your information from intercepted by anyone other than us while it is being transmitted to us. We also utilize other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers), and access control mechanisms to prevent any unauthorized access to systems and data. We taking full attention to ensure that our websites are secure and meeting the industry standard.

##### Others

Except as described in this privacy policy, IGOFX will not use your personal information for any other purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtained your permission to do so.

Selling of information is strictly prohibited for our company staff, affiliates and other third parties, any act discovered may bring to the regulatory punishment.

Should you have any inquiries or concerns regarding the privacy of your information at IGOFX, please write to us at [account@igofx.com](mailto:account@igofx.com)
